From what I'm told, Desmond's anime addiction caused an issue at his church recently.
None are more powerful than Jesus Christ!
There is no way he's beating Goku!
Oh!
What?
You need to leave!
Desmond's father opted to send him to controversial therapist Dr. Victor Blaine as a last-ditch effort to help him.
As you can see, Dr. Blaine, my son is out of control, and I don't know what to do.
I would start with confiscating that pillow.
I'll try to take it from him once.
But when I picked it up, it was as hard as a rock!
Wow!
I think someone should probably check Desmond's hard drive.
Desmond, get that pillow off of my couch. It smells.
That pillow is my girlfriend!
And her name is Miku.